吸血鬼后裔前情提要  我知道怎么找回
Previously on Legacies... I found a way to bring back
所有人的马里之洼记忆了
everyone's Malivore memories.
兰登  我爱你
Landon, I love you.
怪物们不是唯一的问题
Monsters aren't the only problem.
我必须离开  他们一定会跟着我
So I have to leave, knowing that they'll follow me.
当明晚月亮升到最高时  西穆就会衰变
When the moon reaches its apex tomorrow night... Simu-me will disintegrate.
这是任何人都能想到的唯一能关闭入口的方式    我的意识
It's the only way anyone can think of to close the portal   - My consciousness
会传给下一个我杀了的人
will transfer to the next person I cut.
没错  我用咒语改变了你的外形
Ah, yes, I did a spell to alter your appearance.
把你变成了我能想到的
Turn you into the most vile thing
最丑陋的东西
I could imagine.
这不还是我吗
I just look like me.
- 所以说我做的很好  - 我以为你更想看着
- Then I nailed it.  - Huh. I thought you'd rather
兰登那张小帅脸
stare at Landon's sad little face.
抱歉
Sorry.
实话说  我很高兴你在这儿
To be honest, I'm glad you're here.
你显然很恨我  所以为什么这么说
You clearly hate me, so I can't imagine why.
在你把我扔进坑里之前
Because there's still time for you to come to your senses
还是有时间恢复理智的
before you toss me into the pit.
第一  那是个沟
One, it's more of a ditch;
第二  我很期待这么做
two, I'm really looking forward to it;
第三  困住你的这个魔法身体
and three, you're trapped inside a magically created body
午夜就会失效
that expires at midnight.
别废话了
Save your breath.
没人会来救你的
There's no one coming to save you.
你是自掘坟墓  自作自受
You're going into a grave you dug for yourself.
天啊  下雪了
Oh, my God, it's snowing.
我的天啊
Oh, boy.
嘿
Hey!
不公平  我又没看到你
No fair. Wasn't even looking.
好吧
Okay.
凯勒布
Kaleb.
这到底是怎么了
What the hell is going on?
别当吝啬鬼了  霍普  圣诞节到了
Don't be a Scrooge, Hope. It's Christmas.
Scrooge是查尔斯狄更斯的小说《圣诞颂歌》中的主要人物
后指自私  不愿意分享或给予的吝啬鬼
谁说的  才十月
No. It's October.
圣诞节是一种精神意识
Christmas is a state of mind.
是一种气氛
It's a feeling in the air.
现在  你感觉到了吗
Now... you feeling it?
绝对感觉到了点什么
Definitely feeling something.
吸血鬼后裔
这个圣诞节格外暴力
第2季   第8集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
我在
* I'm *
梦想
* Dreaming *
白色的  - 我尽快赶过来了
* Of a white... * - I got here as fast as I could.
来的路上
On the drive over,
到处都堆了雪人
I saw snowmen going up all over town.
孩子们在滑雪
Kids on sleds
大人们也像傻子一样跑来跑去
and adults running around like idiots, stringing up
挂圣诞灯  喝热可可
Christmas lights, drinking cocoa.
翻 译  肉萨
谁在说热可可
Did someone say "cocoa"?
这不是好事  多利安
This is bad, Dorian.
这肯定是另一个怪物干的
This has to be the work of another monster.
翻 译  MonicaSmiles
上一个怪物留下的预言
And the last one gave us a prophecy
我们还没想明白
that we need to figure out,
赶紧把音乐关了
so you need to turn that music off,
回来专心干活
and get your head in the game.
里克  你需要把那些破事忘了
And you need to get your ass off the naughty list, Ric.
翻 译  煎饼
听到了吗
Okay?
所以  先尝尝
So, like I said,
翻 译  Carousel
热可可  然后我们再聊
cocoa, and then we can talk about
你想聊的话题
whatever it is you want to talk about.
你到底在担心什么
Now, what were you so worried about?
我  想不起来了
I, uh... don't remember.
特效：小螺号
白色的
* Of a white *
圣诞节
* Christmas *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
校 对   MonicaSmiles
我写的每一张
* With every Christmas card *
特 效   麦 斯
圣诞卡
* I write *
都祝你幸福
* May your days be merry *
开心
* And bright... *
萨尔兹曼医生  我需要你帮忙
Dr. Saltzman. I need your help.
你穿的这是什么
What are you wearing?
多利安给我的
Dorian had an extra one.
我可真幸运
Lucky me, right?
没有  里克  我们才幸运
No, Ric. We're the lucky ones.
萨尔兹曼医生要跟我们一起过圣诞节了
Because Dr. Saltzman is gonna spend Christmas with us.
谢谢  谢谢你们
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
丽兹
Lizzie!
知道了  霍普  你回来了
We get it, Hope. You're back.
现在你可以消失了
Now disappear again.
谢天谢地  你还是那么讨厌
Ah. You're still a bitch. Thank God.
什么
What?
- 发生什么了  - 我不知道
- What is happening? - I don't know.
好像除了咱俩  全校的人都很开心
It's like everyone in the school is happy except for us.
过于开心了
Too happy.
毛骨悚然的开心
Like scary happy.
甚至是喜庆  他们都以为是圣诞节了
Merry, even. They all think that it's Christmas.
现在下雪也没起什么好作用
And the snow probably doesn't help.
下雪了  怎么会
It's snowing? How?
又有怪物来了吧  我猜
Uh, another monster, I'm guessing.
太可怕了
This is terrible news.
这是他妈的秋天  不是冬天
It's freaking fall. Not winter.
那我该穿什么呢
What am I gonna wear?
路上穿的那种
Something to travel in?
你现在需要马上出发
I'm gonna need you to hit the road.
你想让我去找佛罗多·巴金斯
You want me to quest for Frodo Baggins,
是不是
don't you?
我以为怪物已经不追他了
I thought that the monsters weren't after him now.
我们也不知道他们要干什么
We don't know what they want,
也不知道他们的同伙是谁
or even who they're working for anymore.
我只希望兰登安全
I just need Landon to be safe.
好吧
Fine.
说个定位咒  然后我就去莫多
A little locator spell and then off to Mordor I go.
我带礼物来的
I come bearing gifts.
其实我是来求和的
More like a peace offering, really.
我以为咱们三个
I thought that the three of us
已经没事了
had already made peace.
可是  整个学年我都表现得不好
Well, this whole school year, I have been really naughty.
没像个妹妹一样支持你们
I've not been the supportive sister that I want to be.
还有兰登的事情
And then there's Landon.
我真的不应该嫉妒
It was wrong of me to be jealous
哪怕他下意识的选了你
when his subconscious just chose you.
但是谢天谢地  圣诞节就是
But thankfully, Christmas
要我们互相宽恕的  对吧
is all about forgiveness, right?
吃饼干吗
Cookie?
快去
Run.
什么口味的饼干
What kind of cookie?
哥们  你不用送我礼物
Dude, you didn't have to get me anything.
咱们根本不知道我生日
I mean, we don't even know
具体是哪天  只知道是这个月
when my birthday is, just that it's this month.
所以今天跟其他日子没区别  打开吧
Okay, then today's as good a day as any. Open it up.
这是
Um, it's...
什么鬼
I have no idea.
你被困在狼形态的时候
So while you were trapped in wolf form,
我让乔西做了个血缘咒语  看有没有你的祖先
I had Josie do a lineage spell to see if you had any ancestors
知道怎么把你变回来
who might know how to turn you back.
我觉得可能希望不大
I figured it was a long shot,
可是她找到线索了
but she got a hit.
是你父母
Your parents.
我父母已经死了  兰
My parents are dead, Lan.
我们都以为如此
That's what we thought.
可是把你养大到十岁的人
But the people who raised you till you were ten
不是你的亲生父母
weren't your real parents.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
因为定位咒对死人
Because locator spells don't work
不起作用
on dead bodies.
而这个直接指向
This is leading us straight to...
北卡罗莱纳州
North Carolina.
这辆车就是去那儿的吗
The same place that this bus is going?
我看着你煎熬很久了
I've seen how much you've been struggling.
觉得跟你父母见个面也许能让治好你
I thought maybe meeting your parents might help you heal.
你决定吧  拉斐尔
It's your call, Rafael.
用冬青枝
* Deck the halls *
装饰厅堂
* With boughs of holly *
* Fa-la-la-la-la *
* La-la-la-la *
这是快乐的季节
* 'Tis the season to be jolly... *
嫌疑人名单
1  冰霜杰克
2  热守财奴
3  雪怪
4  圣诞怪杰
5  结霜雪人
我这忙着呢
I'm trying to work!
你们要是不赶紧给我滚滚滚开
So if you don't fa-la-la-la leave,
我就给你们每人再打一个洞
I'm gonna give you all another piercing.
看来你需要我帮忙感受下节日气氛啊
Sounds like someone could use a little help
你想帮忙吗
getting in the spirit. You want to help?
帮我找把斧子吧
Find me an ax.
那看来你是不要喝蛋酒了
So that's a neg on the nog?
我要搞清楚什么怪物让大家都这么开心
I need to figure out what monster's making everyone
然后弄死这个怪物
so freaking merry, then kill it.
你也太淘气了  霍普
Whoa. That's naughty as hell, Hope.
我可得尽可能的让圣诞老人喜欢我
I got to do all I can to make it on Santa's nice list.
因为我每年圣诞节都在许愿得到一个东西
'Cause I've been asking for this one thing
但我从来没得到
every Christmas and, uh, I never got it.
不过我希望今年可以实现
But I'm hoping that this is the year.
太好喝了  你确定不整点蛋酒吗
Hell yeah. You sure you don't want to hit this?
如果我要开始整事情了  我就停不下来了
If I started hitting stuff now, I might never stop.
肯定这里还有跟我一样悲催的人吧
There's got to be someone around here as miserable as I am.
你说得对  我很悲催
You're right. I am miserable.
所以我为啥还要帮你呢
So why would I help you?
相信我  我也希望有其他选择
Believe me, I wish that there was another option,
但你是这里唯一一个没有在吃什么
but you're the only one around here that's not
无花果布丁的人了
eating figgy pudding.
不过好的一面来看  我这么悲催
On the bright side, me being miserable
肯定就是我能够免疫圣诞节气氛的原因了
must be why I'm immune to the Christmas spirit.
那你的借口是什么
What's your excuse?
我以前很喜欢过节的
I used to love the holidays.
但是
But...
我失去了所有家人  一切都变了
I lost a lot of my family, and everything changed.
大家都在我周围感恩他们
Everyone running around here all thankful
拥有的一切
for what they have...
让你意识到你失去了太多
You realize what you're missing.
怎么了
What?
如果有人可以感同身受孤单
If anyone can relate to being alone,
那就是我了
it's me.
我连个圣诞节都没过过
I've never even had a Christmas.
没错了
That's it.
要我帮你搞清楚你的怪物是什么吗
You want my help figuring out your monster?
那就让我大吃大喝
Let me eat, drink and be merry
这辈子快乐一次吧
for once in my life.
好好爽一次
Go out with a bang.
那么
Now...
该去找找老熟人了
...should old acquaintance be forgot?
走啊  马上就到了
Come on, we're almost there.
你还记得上一次你想
Uh, do you remember the last time
让一对父子团聚
that you tried to reunite
- 是什么结局吗  - 我只是想让你考虑一下
a father and a son? I just need you to consider
当乔西恢复我们所有人记忆的时候
that when Josie returned all of our memories,
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
我记起了所有进入马里之洼大坑的人
I remembered everyone that went into the Malivore pit,
不仅仅是霍普
and it wasn't just Hope.
还有你妈妈
Your mom.
跟她见面是跟我想象的一样开心吗
Was meeting her everything I hoped it would be?
并不
No.
但我也很开心我去做了
But I'm really glad I did.
我也想给你这个机会
I just wanted to give you the same chance.
我能理解
And I hear that.
哥们  我只需要你一个家人就够了
Bro, you are the only family that I need.
所以我们还是继续走吧
So let's-let's just keep moving
省得一会又被 别的怪物追上了
before another monster catches up with us.
- 拉夫  别  - 放开我
Raf, please... Let go of me!
我不行
I-I can't...
现在没办法面对这个
I can't deal with this right now.
- 我就是  - 没事的
I just... Hey. It's okay.
走吧  我们走就行了
Let's just get out of here. Let's just get out of here.
你们俩最好跟我来
I think you boys better come with me.
好了  大家把彩带传开
All right, pass those ribbons around.
把你的圣诞愿望写在彩带上
Everybody write down your Christmas wish on them.
不要让别人看到
Don't let anyone see it.
写完之后  把你的彩带
Then when you're done, I want you to toss your ribbon
扔到火里
into the fire.
给你
There you go.
抱歉呀  佩德罗
My bad, Pedro.
我和圣诞老人还有事情没办完呢
Me and Santa got some unfinished business.
彩带还有的是呢
More where that came from.
我们欢笑又歌唱
* Oh, what fun it is to ride *
马儿铃声响
* In a one-horse open sleigh... *
你的愿望是什么  乔
What's your wish, Jo?
我要是说出来就不能实现了呀  对吧
Well, if I tell you that, it won't come true, remember?
马儿铃声响
* One-horse open sleigh *
奔驰过田野
* O'er the fields we go *
给老爸的完美礼物
我们欢笑又歌唱
* Laughing all the way *
叮叮当叮叮当
* Bells on bobtails ring *
令人精神多欢畅
* Making our spirits bright... *
你还真是无尽之坑的儿子呢
Wow, you really are the son of a bottomless pit.
把滑雪歌儿唱
* A sleighing song tonight *
谢了
Thanks.
来  转过去
Here. Turn.
别拖延了
Quit stalling.
快告诉我我要找什么  省的我失去耐心了
Tell me what I'm looking for before I run out of goodwill
结果可就不会那么欢乐了
towards mud men and there are unpleasant consequences.
要我说啊
Mm. My best guess?
克朗普斯
The Krampus.
克朗普斯是什么
What the hell is a Krampus?
是那个会把所有的冰雪
Well, it's the monster that brought
带到城里的怪物
all this snow and ice to town.
它认为自己是反圣诞老人
And think of it as the anti-Santa.
圣诞老人会给乖孩子礼物对吧
Santa Claus rewards good boys and girls, right?
克朗普斯是相反的
Well, the Krampus does the opposite.
它会寻求恨意和愤怒
It seeks out hatred and anger
而不是平和与愉悦
instead of peace and joy.
我们现在周围 真的充满了平和与愉悦
We're literally surrounded by peace and joy.
铃儿响叮当
* Jingle all the way *
今晚滑雪多快乐
* Oh, what fun it is to ride... *
很快就不会了
Not for long.
你刚刚干了什么
What did you just do?
你应该为我骄傲啊  霍普
You should be proud of me, Hope.
我从你的剧本里面拿掉了一页呢
I took a page out of your playbook.
我们坐在雪橇上
* It is to ride... *
我又找到一个漏洞了
I found another loophole.
封印
Cloustrum.
你被封在这个房间里了
You're spelled inside this room.
告诉我  你到底许了什么愿
Now, what exactly did you wish for?
你很快就会知道了
You'll find out soon enough.
随便你怎么说  我今年可是非常不乖呢
Because as you can attest, I've been a very bad boy this year.
不欢乐的后果  还记得吗
Unpleasant consequences, remember?
你到底
Now what
许了什么愿
did you wish...
一个救星
A savior.
你想要保护兰登对吧
You want to protect Landon, right?
别担心  克朗普斯会来救我
Well, don't worry. The Krampus is coming to rescue me
而不是追杀他了
instead of going after him.
而且会杀掉任何足够愚蠢阻挡它的人
And it'll kill anyone dumb enough to get in its way.
不管我们有没有准备好
Not if we're ready for it.
你说的我们  是学校里
By "we," do you mean the school
借着过节喝得烂醉的傻小孩吗
full of idiot kids drunk on Christmas cheer?
还是跑来跑去真的喝得烂醉
Or the grown men running around
还相信圣诞老人是真的的成年人呢
actually drunk, believing that Santa Claus is real?
祝你可以破解掉
Good luck dampening
圣诞节气氛  让他们听你的话吧
their spirits and getting them to listen to you.
这个交给我就行了
You leave that to me.
你能不能
Would you
真的不要再
literally stop
按我的按钮（惹我生气）了
pushing my buttons?
终于讲话了啊
So, she finally speaks, eh?
抱歉  不过
Sorry. But...
我真是很喜欢现代机械啊
modern machinery fascinates me.
这个费油的破车已经又老又旧了
This gas-guzzler is older than dirt.
是我和乔西16岁成人生日的时候我爸朋友送的
My dad's friend gave it to me and Josie for our sweet 16.
那我们应该停下来加油啊
We should stop for fuel, then.
我也想好好吃顿饭
I could also use a proper meal.
你的意思是
By which you mean...
谁愿意加油谁去吧
Uh, whoever else stops for fuel.
没错  而且出发前你就该吃东西的
Yes. Mm. You should've eaten before we left.
你真是让我很蒙圈  伊丽莎白
You know, you confound me, Elizabeth.
你给我做了这个日光戒指的时候
You know, when you made me this daylight ring,
我真以为是个小诡计来着
I assumed it was a ruse.
我本来以为这是一个诡计
你只是想和我待在一起而不想
That you merely wanted to spend time together beyond
被学校该死的规矩束缚着
the loathsome confines of your school.
那你就以为错了
Well, then, you assumed wrong.
你之所以会在这里  是因为你会让我
The only reason that you're here is because you keep me
一直感觉不愉快
perpetually un-jolly.
我们都知道不是这样的
Well, we both know that's not true.
显然  我在这儿是因为你喜欢我
I'm here because you fancy me, obviously.
你这车开得跟醉鬼似的
You command this vessel like a drunken pirate.
我刚看见了几头鹿
I just saw some deer.
如果你很饿的话
If you're so hungry,
不如你去吃小鹿斑比吧
why don't you go eat Bambi?
这算是某种测试吗
Is this some kind of test?
你说是就是
You bet your ass it is.
他让我想要看着你
* And he makes me want to watch you move *
四处走动
* Around *
我非常爱你
* I love you too much... *
而你失败了
And you failed.
大家可以
Can I have
听我说句话吗
everyone's attention?
大家听我说句话
I need everyone's attention.
我有坏消息
I have bad news.
一只克朗普斯正冲我们过来
A Krampus is headed our way.
四分五裂
Concido.
好吧  我也不想大发雷霆毁了这里的一切
All right! Didn't want to deploy the nuclear option,
但圣诞老人并不存在
but Santa's not real.
他只是个传说而已  你们现在就像一群孩子
He's a myth. And you're all acting like a bunch of children.
所以我们
So let's just
梨树上的鹧鸪是圣诞节的象征
把鹧鸪放回到梨树上
put the partridge back in the pear tree
赶紧长大变成熟点儿
and grow the hell up.
她说得没错
She's right.
这一切都美好得令人难以相信
I... This was all too good to be true.
我
I...
我不知道我们到底是怎么了
I, uh, I don't know what came over us.
好了  你们都听见她说得话了
All right, you all heard her.
多里安  去查查文献
Dorian, hit the books,
弄清楚克朗普斯是怎么行动的
figure out how the Krampus operates.
乔西  凯勒布
Josie, Kaleb,
我们得给这个家伙设个陷阱  其它人
we need to set a trap for this thing. Everyone else,
带孩子们去睡觉  然后把武器都拿过来
get the kids to bed and gather weapons.
谁给我拿一把弩过来
And someone bring me a crossbow.
这完全是个误会
This is all a-a misunderstanding.
我们只是迷路了
We were just lost.
一个关狼人的笼子
A werewolf cage?
我看到了你的眼睛
I saw your eyes.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
你在经历着什么
What you're going through.
你是个狼人
You're a werewolf.
不
No.
但我曾爱过一个
But I was in love with one.
我是在阿富汗认识的露西亚
I met Lucia in Afghanistan.
但如果她知道自己杀人后会发生什么
But if she'd known what would happen after she took a life,
她绝对不会参军的
she never would've enlisted.
我们回国之后
When we got back to the States,
她和很多人都有共同的表现
she was like a lot of us:
无法控制怒气  记忆力损失
fits of anger, memory loss,
害怕站在人群中
trouble with crowds.
典型的创伤后应激障碍
A classic case of PTSD.
直到第一次满月的来临
Until that first full moon hit.
你为什么  你为什么一直用
Uh, why do you... why do you keep talking
过去式来描述她
about her in the past tense?
发生什么事了
What happened?
露西亚是我见过最勇敢的军人
Lucia was the bravest soldier I ever knew.
我唯一一次看见她感到害怕
The only time I ever saw her scared
是在她发现自己怀孕的时候
was when she found out she was pregnant.
你们俩  有过一个孩子吗
You two had a-a kid?
在她知道自己怀孕后的第一个满月
First full moon after she learned she was expecting,
她消失了
she was just gone.
我找了她很多年  但是
I searched for her for years, but...
像她那样的军人  如果不想被人发现的话  是永远不会被发现的
a soldier like her who doesn't want to be found never will be.
但我从那之后每天都在想
But I thought about her and our baby
她和我们的孩子
every day since.
所以你该告诉我你为什么会在这里了
So it's time you told me why you're here.
因为你不仅和你妈妈的眼睛很像  拉斐尔
Because you have more than just your mother's eyes, Rafael.
圣诞快乐  克朗普斯
Merry Christmas, Krampus.
我猜你有东西要给我
I believe you have something for me.
不  那不是我要的东西
No, that-that's not what I asked for.
我想要另一个三叉戟
I wanted another trident.
你特么在干嘛啊  你应该来救我的
What the hell are you doing? You were supposed to save me.
我猜你就是克朗普斯
I'm guessing you're the Krampus.
咒语
Mittent.
我叫霍普
I'm Hope.
圣诞节让我感觉压力很大
And I find the holidays really stressful.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
该死的  那家伙可能会去任何地方
Damn it. That thing could be anywhere.
等等  我还以为
Wait. I thought
我爸爸会派克朗普斯来救我
my father was bringing the Krampus to save me.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
他肯定已经知道我打算
He must have known I was planning
跳进一个新的身体里再骗他一次
to jump into a new body and screw him over again.
怎么知道的
How?
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
但如果你放我走的话
But if you let me go,
我可以在克朗普斯杀我之前
I can make it to the portal
到达传送门那里
before the Krampus kills me.
想得美  但如果你再骗我一次
Nice try, but "fool me once" and all...
如果我能证明我是站在
What if there was a way that I could prove to you
你这一边呢
that I'm on your side?
证明我说的是实话
That I'm telling the truth.
我以为自己已经控制了愤怒
I thought I had laid the anger under control,
但是  但我依然还会感到它
but... but it just came back
并且比起以前更糟  你知道吗
worse than ever, you know?
上学确实有用  因为那里有
Being at school-- it helped, because there was-there was
其它像我一样的人  但事实证明
other people like me. But it turned out that
那并不是属于我们的地方
it-it wasn't the right place for us, you know.
有时候你不得不为了保护自己爱的人而离开
Sometimes you have to leave to protect the people you love.
我想这就是妈妈丢下我的原因
I think that's why my mom gave me up.
相信我  我能理解
Believe me, I get it.
我知道逃跑像是
I know running away can feel like
唯一的选择
it's the only option.
你确定你不想喝点儿什么吗  兰登
Sure I can't get you something to drink, Landon?
不用了  沃尔特
I'm good, Walt.
谢谢你为我所做的一切
Thank you. For everything.
我到外面去透透气
Um, I'm just gonna grab some air,
如果你不介意的话
if that's cool with you.
可以啊
Uh, yeah.
兰登
Hey, Lan.
我想也许你让我们来这儿是对的
I think maybe you were right about coming here.
上车  霍比特人
Hop in, hobbit.
莉兹
Lizzie?
再说一句废话  我就亲自把你扔进
One more word and I will feed you to the flames
末日火山的火焰中
of Mount Doom myself.
灯火通明
Illustrant.
正中心脏
Straight in the heart.
这才是杀死克朗普斯的正确方式
That's how you kill a Krampus.
有人想喝热可可吗
Anyone want some cocoa?
好啊  为什么不呢  毕竟过圣诞节呢
Yeah, sure, why not? It's Christmas.
等等  你俩还这么开心呢
Wait, you two are still merry.
如果它已经死了  为什么这场疯狂没有停止呢
If it's dead, then why hasn't this lunacy stopped?
所有人都退后
Everyone stay back.
不管那里面有什么  它要出来了
Whatever's in that thing is coming out.
在这个特别的夜晚  谁不想变快乐呢
Who wouldn't be merry on this special night?
这是圣诞节的魔力  迈克尔森女士
It's the magic of Christmas, Miss Mikaelson.
这是一年中最美好的时候
It's the most wonderful time of the year.
圣诞老人
Santa?
- 难以相信你是真实存在的  - 你当然可以相信了
- I can't believe you're real. - Well, of course you can.
亲爱的霍普
You see, my dear Hope,
只要你相信  事情就能变成现实
belief is what makes things real.
请讲
Yes?
你怎么会知道她的名字呢
How did you know her name?
因为每个人都曾是个孩子
Because everyone was a child once,
而我记着你们每一个人
and I remember each and every one.
再说了  像阿拉里克这样的名字想忘记都难
Besides, a name like Alaric is pretty tough to forget.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
吼吼吼
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
我  我必须感谢你们所有人
I-I must thank all of you
又把我带了回来
for bringing me back.
这么多年真的是很辛苦
It's been hard, all these years,
被困在那个可怕和黑暗的地方
being trapped in that awful, dark place,
没办法在全世界播撒欢乐
unable to spread joy around the world...
都是因为你
...because of you.
我还以为我把那个鬼东西给杀了呢
Thought I killed that damn thing.
注意用词  萨尔茨曼博士
Language, Dr. Saltzman.
别因为你的失手而自责了
Don't blame yourself for missing.
克朗普斯的心眼特别的小
The Krampus' heart is very small,
这个
and this...
是我的战争
is my fight.
等一下  霍普  别动手  你听见他说的了
Wait, Hope, no. You heard the man.
这是私人恩怨
This one's personal.
你以为你可以偷走圣诞节  是吗
So you thought you could steal Christmas, did you?
吼吼
Ho, ho...
不
...no.
之前你抛下了霍普和乔西
Leaving Hope and Josie without having
连说出原因的勇气都没有
the balls to say why was one thing,
现在你又想抛弃拉斐尔
but now you're ditching Raf?
只要怪物们还在追我
As long as monsters are after me,
他就会有危险  我需要找个地方
he's in danger, too. I needed to find someplace
能保证他的安全的地方
where I knew he'd be safe.
那你有什么计划  哈克·芬恩
So what is your plan, Huck Finn--
- 搭火车吗  - 我唯一的计划
- ride the rails? - My only plan
就是确保所有人都不会因为我而受伤
is to make sure that nobody else gets hurt because of me,
因为那样真是太糟糕了
because that really sucks.
和我一起回学校吧  面对霍普和乔西
Come back to the school with me, face Hope and Josie,
他们会帮助你
and then they will help you face
一起面对接下来的一切
whatever comes next.
我们都会帮你的
We all will.
你觉得怎么样
What do you say?
我觉得你们
I say you people talk
说的太多却一点行动都没有
entirely too much when action is required.
祝你圣诞快乐
* We wish you a Merry Christmas *
祝你圣诞和新年快乐
* We wish you a Merry Christmas and a happy New Year... *
他可真快啊
Dude's fast. * We wish you *
祝你圣诞快乐
* A Merry Christmas... *
特别快
Like, really fast.
祝你圣诞
* We wish you a Merry Christmas *
和新年快乐
* And a Happy New Year *
好消息送给你
* Good tidings to you... *
否则你认为我怎么可能一个晚上飞能到那么多家去呢
How do you think I make it to all those houses in one night?
给我们来些无花果布丁吧
* Oh, bring us some figgy pudding *
* Oh, bring us some figgy pudding... *
你最好小心点
You better watch out!
给我们来些无花果布丁和欢呼吧
* Bring us some figgy pudding and a cup of cheer *
哎哎哎
* Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi *
圣诞老人
Santa.
哎哎哎
* Oi, oi, oi *
不吃到我们就不会离开
* We won't go until we get some *
所以请给我们吧
* So bring it out here *
祝你圣诞快乐
* We wish you a Merry Christmas... *
看见没
See?
心真的非常小
Very small indeed.
祝你圣诞快乐
* We wish you a Merry Christmas *
祝你圣诞和新年快乐
* We wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. *
问题应该解决了  你的驾驶技术可真够差的
Well, this settles the matter. You are a terrible pilot.
我真的想不到  还有比跟你待在一起
I didn't think that being with you
更悲催的事情了
could get any more miserable.
你生气
You are only angry
是因为你试图抛弃我的计划失败了
because your plan to abandon me has failed.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
- 把你的衬衫穿回去  - 我跟踪你的时候
- Put your shirt back on. - You know, I sussed it
就意识到了
when I was tracking you down.
这就是为什么你把我带来了  是不是
That is the reason you brought me along, wasn't it?
这样以来  你就好把我像个小狗一样
So you could just, what, ditch me like
抛弃掉
some unwanted puppy.
更像是一个咖啡壶我觉得
I mean, more like a perk, really.
你不应该在学校
You shouldn't be at the school.
你称呼我的朋友们为防风草
You call my friends parsnips.
不  他们是红萝卜
No, they're turnips.
好吧  不管他们是哪种植物
Okay, whatever vegetable that they are,
反正他们不喜欢你
they don't like you.
没人喜欢你
No one does.
除了你  伊丽莎白
Except for you, Elizabeth.
最后声明一次
For the last time,
我不再喜欢你了
I don't "fancy" you or whatever.
我甚至可能会恨你  塞巴斯蒂安
I might even hate you, Sebastian.
你让我觉得自己像个疯子
You made me think that I was crazy.
也许我们都疯了
Well, perhaps we both are.
因为我喜欢你  伊丽莎白
For I fancy you, Elizabeth.
中世纪的女人也对马甲线欲罢不能么
Did that line work in the Middle Ages?
当然
Yes. Yes, it did,
还有腹肌
as did my abdominal muscles,
但是最重要的是
but all that truly matters is that
现在都能派上用场了
it's working now.
才没有
No, it isn't.
有的
Mm, 'tis.
- 没有  - 有
- 'Tis not. - 'Tis.
没有
'Tis not.
有
'Tis.
好吧  你可
Okay, you
真是让人忍受不了
are insufferable.
但是幸运的是
But lucky for me,
但是有个动脉瘤咒语
there is something called an aneurysm spell. Ah,
你学不会
which you cannot cast.
不碰我你可施不了咒语
not without touching me.
我说了
I said
把你的衬衫穿上
put your shirt back on.
好吧  随便你
Okay, you know what? Whatever.
你忘记了在后备箱里还有一个
You are forgetting that there is a perfectly good dead phoenix
昏迷的凤凰呢
in the trunk.
你也忘了我是个危险人物
And you are forgetting that I am dangerous.
别说话
Stop talking.
行动起来
Action is required.
真没想到我还能再跟你说上话
Can't say I expected to talk to you again.
我也是
Me neither.
但是在我死之前
But before I die,
我想告诉你有件事你错了
I wanted to tell you that you're wrong.
我不恨你
I don't hate you.
你在我身上施的真言咒
And that the truth spell you cast on me
还一直起作用呢
is still working, obviously.
雪融化了
The snow melted.
我想这说明克朗普斯死了
I'm assuming that means the Krampus is dead?
没错  圣诞老人杀了他
Yup. Santa Claus killed him.
这个圣诞
This Christmas
真是惊人的暴力啊
was surprisingly violent.
这样的话
In that case,
我就可以直接去传送门了
I have a clean run to the portal.
榭寄生
* Mistletoe... *
至少我可以享受生命中
At least I can enjoy the last
最后的十分钟
ten minutes of my life.
好吧
Well...
如果你有什么想说的话
if you want to talk,
你想说多久我都会听
I'll listen for as long as I can.
树木
* The tree... *
我想
I think
我有点嫉妒你  霍普
I'm jealous of you, Hope.
因为你和我一样  都搞砸了  但是
Because you're just as screwed up as I am, but...
你的朋友们仍然爱你
your friends still love you.
会找到我
* Will find me... *
我想我一直相信我父亲也会这样做
Guess I always wanted to believe my father could do the same.
爱在的地方
* Where the love... *
只要你相信  任何事都可以成真
Anything can be real if you believe in it enough.
圣诞快乐  霍普
Merry Christmas, Hope.
圣诞快乐  克拉克
Merry Christmas, Clarke.
圣诞
* For Christmas *
如果
* If only *
只在
* In my *
我梦里
* Dreams. *
你真要走吗
Sure you have to go?
嗯  我得
Yeah, I got
回学校  找人帮个忙
to head back to the school and get myself some help.
你体内流淌着军人的血液
Being a soldier's in your blood.
永远向前
Always moving forward.
我去拿钥匙
I'll get my keys.
至少送你一程
Give you a ride, at least.
或者我可以
Or I could...
坐第一班车走
I could take the first bus out.
那你朋友呢
Uh, what about your friend?
我认识的人里  兰登最擅长生存
Landon's better at surviving than anyone I know.
再说了  我还能跟你学不少东西
Besides, I think I can learn a lot from you.
我是说
I mean, if...
如果你不介意我在你家过夜的话
if you don't mind me, uh, crashing.
真高兴你接受了事实
I am glad you accepted the truth.
你确实很喜欢我的事实
You fancy me very much indeed.
我喜欢和你做爱而已
I fancy sex with you.
其余的尚无定论
The jury's out on all the rest.
多做几次爱就说服你
Would more copulation convince you
我该留在学校了吗
that I should stay at the school?
我
Uh, I-I...
你为什么想留下来
Why would you even want to stay?
除了做爱这点
Besides the copulation.
因为我无处可去
Because I have nowhere else to go.
我在地球上的五百年里
In my five centuries of being on this planet,
人们
little has changed
对待彼此的方式基本没变
in the way that people treat one another.
世界对那些残破之人是残酷的
This world is cruel to those it considers broken.
但塞尔瓦托学校的所有变化
But the Salvatore School, for all its...
不同其他
...aggravations, is different.
那里是我去过最亲切的地方了
It's the kindest place that I have ever been.
所以我才想留下
That's why I want to stay there.
寂静之夜
* Silent night *
前提是你让我留下
If you'll have me.
神圣之夜
* Holy night *
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
你俩干嘛呢
What are you guys doing?
收拾圣诞节的东西
Packing up Christmas.
还没结束呢  因为圣诞老人给你
Well, it's not over yet, because Santa left this
留了这件礼物
for you.
给你了
Then that's for you.
当真
Really?
你觉得这里面是啥
What do you think it is?
是
It's...
完美之物
perfect.
圣婴
* Holy infant *
如此脆弱
* So tender *
如此温和
* And mild *
阿拉里克·萨尔茨曼博士
校长
沉睡在
* Sleep in *
天堂般的
* Heavenly *
宁静之中
* Peace *
睡在
* Sleep in... *
我靠  车不错啊
Damn! Nice ride!
谢了  凯勒布
Thank you, Kaleb.
老实讲  我还是更喜欢我的驯鹿
To be honest, I much prefer my reindeer.
75年的雪佛兰维特都比不上
To a '75 Vette?
恕我失礼
Sorry.
我那个疯叔叔厄尔
My-my crazy-ass Uncle Earl
也有辆一模一样的车
had this exact same car.
我从小就想要一辆了
I've wanted one since I was a kid.
所以过节的时候我们才要送礼物啊
Well, that's why we give gifts during the holiday season.
这提醒我们心怀梦想十分重要
To remind us that it's important to have dreams.
因为有时候
Because sometimes
梦想便会成真
they come true.
圣诞快乐  凯勒布
Merry Christmas, Kaleb.
什么
Wha...
这是真的吗
For real?
圣诞快乐  霍普
Merry Christmas, Hope!
你该说点什么了
This is the part where you say something.
也可以逃避
Or run.
两者都有吧
It's both.
你能在这儿等我一下吗
Can you please just wait right here?
我真的有话对你说
I have something that I really need to tell you. I...
现在还不能说
I just can't until I've had
我得先去找别人
another conversation first.
乔
Hey, Jo.
圣诞快乐咯
Merry Christmas, I guess?
你知道圣诞节怪在哪儿吗
You know what's weird about Christmas?
圣诞节
It's, um...
既最喜乐  亦最忧愁
the happiest and the saddest.
能先从喜乐开始吗
Can we start with the happy?
更冷了
* And it's colder *
人不能求伴侣更好
A person could not ask for a better partner,
更有良心
a better conscience.
而且我知道  你
* And I know you... *
基本上也就你判断力这么差
You are literally the best person that's ever had
决定跟我在一起
the poor judgement to hang out with me.
我们没有今夜  亦没有明天
* We didn't get tonight, we don't have tomorrow... *
我喜欢你笑的样子
I love the way you laugh.
所以  切莫毁掉此刻
* So don't ruin now... *
还有你微微向下的嘴角
And your upside down mouth.
你看电影时的模样
The way your face looks when you watch movies and...
你爱上霍普了
You're in love with Hope.
但那也不代表
But that doesn't mean
我就后悔了
I regret a single second.
如果我们不能
* If we don't move... *
因为你倾国倾城
Because you are beautiful.
一同前行
* Together... *
独一无二
And special.
完美无缺
And... perfect.
我们要怎么呼吸
* How we gonna breathe *
我们要怎么
* How we gonna be *
做正确的事不该这么难啊
And doing the right thing should never be this hard.
我还以为离开是最好的选择
I thought leaving was the right thing to do.
一切都太吵了
* Everything's loud... *
但我错了
But I was wrong.
所以我要回来对你说
That's what I came back to say.
我爱你  霍普·迈克尔森
I love you, Hope Mikaelson.
我不怎么记得你之时  就爱你
I-I loved you when I couldn't remember you.
我爱你  所以我现在站在这里
I love you as I'm standing here right now.
霍普  即便我死  也是爱你
Hope, I loved you when I was dead.
细如尘埃
* The tiniest thing... *
我会永远爱你
I think I always will.
但我们没有今夜
* But we didn't get tonight *
亦没有明天
* We don't have tomorrow *
我受够了悄悄话
* So I'm done whispering... *
轮到你了
This is the part where you say...
我也爱你
That I love you, too...
兰登·卡比
Landon Kirby.
我爱你的时候你都不知道
God, I loved you when you didn't even know it.
尽管你当时穿着一身球衣
Despite the way you've looked in a football uniform.
让我开口吧
* And let me say *
在黑暗的黎明之中
* In the dark of the morning... *
还有一句话
Then there's only one thing left to say.
只有一件事
* Just one more thing... *
看上面
Look up.
我们怎么能
* How we gonna move *
在一起
* Together? *
靠近我
* Just come closer *
若我们不在
* If we don't move *
一起
* Together *
也要各自安好
* Just keeping the peace *
* Just keeping the peace. *
别担心  老爸
Don't worry, Dad.
圣诞节我会回家的
I'll be home for Christmas.
我还是更喜欢万圣节
Always preferred Halloween, meself.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）